

CONTACT

Pune, Maharashtra, India



+91 7875 416 318



@ dhanashree.gaikwad17@gmail.com



dhanashreegaikwad.com

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

Symbiosis College, Pune University 2008-2011

Web Diploma

Edit Institute 2011-2012

German Language-Intermediate

Symbiosis Institute of Foreign Languages 2011-2012

IT-SKILLS

Sketch Photoshop Axure Adobe XD

HOBBIES









CERTIFICATIONS & TRAININGS

Human Centered Design IDEO

User Research Program SAP

Diploma in Communication Executive

Cambridge University

Member at IDF IDF

DHANASHREE GAIKWAD

USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER

ABOUT ME

I am a disciplined User Experience Designer with around 11 years of experience in designing cross platform applications. I mainly take user-centered, iterative and insight-driven design approach, using future friendly design patterns. I constantly upgrade myself with latest design trends to deliver the best possible experience for clients and users alike.



† 17 April 1990

EXPERIENCE

UX DESIGNER

WESTERN UNION | 2019-PRESENT

I constantly seek to craft a better experience for the user to transfer money across the globe in easiest way. Over a past year, I mainly contributed in building patterns and components in design system, adapt and enhance the experience on Kiosk platform and revamp the eKYC experience to get the customer verification done easily and faster with users converting from 25% to 95%.

UX DESIGN LEAD

KPIT | 2018-2019

I was responsible for revamping an automotive product designed to help bikers and their groups from planning and guiding them through the entire route with the inbuilt GPS capabilities. We designed the better recommendations from the app, covering all their activities. This helped us to provide the entire ecosystem designed for the biking activities, connect in themselves across the country.

SENIOR UX DESIGNER

XORIANT SOLUTION | 2016-2018

I got my hands-on in real estate and manufacturing domain, where I practiced the research techniques for remote users, draw insights from the data collected and testing it back with end users. These practices were applied in an agile and constraint centric assignments like for vendor and contract management portal for Glencore-Shell and UPM portal for UK based clients CONTXT.

UX DESIGNER

COGNIZANT TECHNOLOGY SOLUTION | 2014-2016

I got an opportunity to explore mainly in banking and finance domain in this organization. As a UX designer I contributed in brands like Lloyds banking Group, Spend Management system app for Sanofi, BEM system for World Bank, Healthcare site for Xerox, iWatch app for Chrysler, web banking portal for Credit Suisse and a heldesk portal of Fresenius Medical Care.

UI/UX DESIGNER

FORTUNE COOKIE | 2012-2014

I started off as a UI/UX Designer on an enterprise application 'Onvelop' (Available on itunes & Playstore) and got a thorough training in driving end-to-end research and design process for the product. I also got hands on experience over designing SAP based smartphone app, android tablet launcher for OIOO (China), PC protection Intel app, healthcare social website for VITANECT.